Guide to the Yale University's 300th Anniversary Commemoration Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University's 300th anniversary commemoration records
1995-2002
RU 884
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
35.63
513.96
The records document the work of the Tercentennial Office. Included are the records of Janet Lindrer concerning planning of the tercentennial celebration, correspondence, subject files, video recordings, records of the Tercentennial Planning Committee, and the Tercentennial website. Also included is a poem by John Hollander, a speech by Robin Winks, printed material, news clippings, memorabilia commemorating Yale's 300th anniversary, and records for the Tercentennial celebration in Asia.
Yale University. Tercenntenial Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 2-A (YRG 2-A), Records of the Yale president's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Copies of commercially produced audiovisual materials contained in this collection cannot be made for researcher use outside of the repository.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records document the work of the Tercentennial Office. Included are the records of Janet Lindrer concerning planning of the tercentennial celebration, correspondence, subject files, video recordings, records of the Tercentennial Planning Committee, and the Tercentennial website. Also included is a poem by John Hollander, a speech by Robin Winks, printed material, news clippings, memorabilia commemorating Yale's 300th anniversary, and records for the Tercentennial celebration in Asia.
Anniversaries; Yale University. Office of the Secretary; Yale University -- Anniversaries, etc.; Yale University -- Centennial celebrations, etc.; Yale University. Tercentennial Office
- Program, brochure, and badge commemorating the Connecticut Hall postal card/stamp, 2001; Accession 2002-A-046
  - Program, brochure, and badge commemorating the Connecticut Hall postal card/stamp, 2001 (Box 1)
- Records of Janet Lindner as director of the Tercentennial Office, 1993-2001; Accession 2002-A-090
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - Yale's 250th (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pierson's Thoughts on Yale's 250th (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Harvard's 350th (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Harvard (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Other University -Princeton and Columbia (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ambassadors to 2101 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Report of 1828 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Residential Colleges -History (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Planning Meetings, 1996- 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Charter (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Yale Literary Magazine -Bicentennial (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - RCL -Preparing Yale's Fourth Century (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Seminal Events in Yale's History (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Yale Presidential Inauguration (notes), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Secretary (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Coordinator II, Media (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Planning History -Committee Comments (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Records of the Tercentennial Office, circa 1995-2001; Accession 2002-A-093
  - List of Files (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meetings (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - University Council (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Association of Yale Alumni (AYA)
    - Alumni/International (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Events (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Blue Line Arts (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Events/Ideas (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Education Tours Abroad (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Gifts from Alumni (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Reunions (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Tour and Trip Ideas (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Ronald Konetchy (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Yale AYA (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Yale Clubs (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Yale Club of Hong Kong (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ACADEMIC CENTERS AND DEPARTMENTS
    - Lists Masters Deans Directors Chairs etc., 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - School and Department Liaisons (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Liaison Fax Numbers (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Unions (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Yale Child Study Center (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - SCHOOLS
    - International Security Studies (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Admissions (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Art School (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Athletics (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Divinity /ISM (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Drama (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Economics Dept (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Employee Recognition (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Engineering (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - School of Forestry (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Graduate Professional Schools (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - History Department (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Human Resources (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Law School (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Medical School (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - School of Architecture (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - School of Management (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Whitney Humanities (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Yale Center for Internationaland Area Studies (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Mental Health (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - School of Music (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Science Group (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Yale-China (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - School of Nursing (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - STUDENTS
    - African American Cultural Society (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Directors of Cultural Centers (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Student Groups / Dramat (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Dwight Hall (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Gay and Lesbian Studies (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - GPSS (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Instrumental Groups (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Student Organizations Complete List (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Yale Daily News (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Whiffenpoofs (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Singing Groups (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Yale Glee Club (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - YCC (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - College Council Student Representatives (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Residential Colleges (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Bull Dogs in the Blue Grass (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - History Honor Society (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - L.E.A.P (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Saint Thomas More and Yale (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Student Groups (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Student Groups -Class Day 2001 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Student Outreach (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Yale Herald (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Yale Singing Groups/Addresses/phone numbers/email addresses (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Student Activities (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Communicating with Schools and Campus Groups (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - DEANS
    - Chairs/Deans/Directors (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Deans (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Deans Luncheon (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Deans Meetings (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Council of Masters (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - COLLEGES
    - Former Masters/Current Masters/Deans (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Berkeley College (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Branford College (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Calhoun College (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Davenport College (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Jonathan Edwards College (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Morse College (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Pierson College (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Saybrook College (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Silliman College (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Timothy Dwight College (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Trumbull College (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Residential College Events (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Students: Senior Essays (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Collections (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Collections: Center for British Art (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Machu Picchu (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Kodak/Machu Picchu (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Eli Whitney Museum (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Yale Art Gallery (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Women's Faculty Forum (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - WOMEN AT YALE
    - Women at Yale (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Way Beyond (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - April Weekend (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Gender Matters (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Women's Center (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Tercentennial Poster Contest -Student Submissions (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - LIBRARIES
    - Beinecke Library (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Sterling Library (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Lewis Walpole Library (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - RELIGIOUS DIMENSIONS PREACHER SERIES
    - Religious Dimensions (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - LECURESHIPS
    - DeVane/Stern, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Castle Lectures (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Chubb (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Symposium on Democracy (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - DeVane Lectures/Dean Kronman "democratic vistas", 2001 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Democratic Vistas/Public Forum/C.F. (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - American Democracy/Higher Education (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Gordon Grand Lectureship (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Sillman Lecture (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Tetelman Lectures (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Fall '98 Yale and the External World -Gaddis Smith DeVane Lecture (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Lectureships -Terc -Lecture Series (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Terry Lectureship (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - DeVane/ New Haven Community Component/C.Farrar/D.Vistas (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Timothy Dwight (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - The Yale Report of 1828/A Critique/Trumbull Lecture (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Lectureships Trumbull (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Poynter Fellowship (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Ezra Stiles College (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - STUDENT EVENTS
    - Commencement (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Plays, Parties, Film Series, Singing Groups, Etc. (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Ballet Folklorico (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Prairie Home Companion (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - NEW HAVEN
    - Community Organizations (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - New Haven Historical Society (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Amistad (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Arts Council of New Haven (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Chamber of Commence (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Community Service Projects/New Haven (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Changing the Map (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Hopkins School (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Long Wharf/New Haven Community Organizations (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Festival of Arts and Ideas (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - St. Patrick's Day (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - New Haven Register (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - March 14thNew Haven Meeting (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - New Haven/ Public Lecture Series (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Melanie Ginter (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - New Haven Downtown Guides and Maps (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - New Haven Channel 8 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - New Haven Downtown Coordinating Committee (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - New Haven/Empowerment Zone (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - New Haven/Home Ownership (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - New Haven/Marketing New Haven (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - New Haven Preservation Trust Board of Directors (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - New Haven/Schools (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - New Haven Partnership (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - New Haven/Sankofa Cultural Arts Festival (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - New Haven/St. Patrick's Day parade (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - New Haven/Teacher's institute (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Outreach: Global/Lawrence Link (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - New Haven Symphony Orchestra (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Shubert Theatre (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - WYBC (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Yale Club of New Haven (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - CO-OP (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - TERCENTENNIAL KICKOFF WEEKEND
    - Seal of the City, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Open House (Box 4, Folder 165 - 166)
    - Opening Ceremony (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Chubb Lecture (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Media Strategy (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Board of Governors/Mory's Open House (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - APRIL 2001 WEEKEND
    - General (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Celebration of Culture Creeds and Creativity (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Book Fest (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Attendance/Rooms/Etc. (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - People to Think/Invite (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Academic Procession, 2001 October (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Convocation, 2001 October 5 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - October Convocation Fanfare (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Attendance Estimates, 2001 October (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Benediction (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Celebration at Cross Campus (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Charter Wekends -Hotels and Rooms (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Guild of Carillonneurs (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Invocation (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Multi Faith Service (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Yale Bowl October Signage (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Oct. Convocation Sponsorship (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - October Weekend Invites (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - OPS Committee (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Receptions (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Rolling Stones (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Tercentennial Weekend Facilities (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Volunteers (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Tercentennial Charter Weekend -Event Firms (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - October Tickets (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Terc. Weekend -Satellite Broadcast/Brian Dowling Proposal (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - LARC (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Saturday Night Evening LARC (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Tracking Weather Patterns (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Sunset (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Musical Planning (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Old Saybrook (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Descendants of Yale Founders (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Dining/Food/Wine (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Facilities/Planning (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Facilities/Dining (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Summer Facilities Planning Committee Fall Meeting (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Handicap Access (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Meeting Spaces (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Ticketing (Box 5, Folder 210 - 211)
  - EVENTS PLANNING
    - Events Planning (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Update Bulletin Confirmations (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Conventures (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Events Planning (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - The Creative Group (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Expert Events (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Hanzon Productions (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Hill Knowlton (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Andy Rubinoff (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Jack Terrace (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Public Relations Firms (Box 5, Folder 222)
  - SPECIAL PROJECTS
    - Web Site (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Calendar Program Design (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Child Study -Yale Young Readers (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Design (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Calendar (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Seamus Heaney (special projects) (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Paul Collard "Tantalus" (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Tercentennial Medal (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Postal Cards (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Calendar Ideas (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - David Gergen (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Physical Restoration National Historic landmark (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Poem (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Cole Porter (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Renovation Projects (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Sculptures (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Song (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Hymn (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Timeline (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - United Nations (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Yale Historic Trail (special project) (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Printed Materials (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Yale Stationary (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Renovation Projects (Box 5, Folder 246)
  - FILM PROJECTS
    - A Hero for Daisy (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Film-Film Possibilities (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Jodie Foster (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Film/Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Film Video Notes (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Indira Nehru Gandi Film and Information (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Lighting Designer (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - David Milch (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Greenwald (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - TV/Film (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Mirror World (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Rosen (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Women at Yale (Box 5, Folder 259)
  - LOGO
    - Logo (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Logo Sketches (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - Trademark (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - "Two by Four" 2x4 (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - PUBLICITY
    - Tercentennial Posters (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Posters (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Communications -Eric Moffitt (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Media Plan (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Briefings (Box 6, Folder 268)
    - Editorial Help (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Media Plans for Tercentennial (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Media Contacts (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - NPR (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Press (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Publicity Agents (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - WTNH Weather Camps, 2000 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Publicity General (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - PR2 (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Publishers (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Radio (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Streaming Video (Box 6, Folder 280)
    - TED 7 CD ROMS (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - Telecommunications (Box 6, Folder 282)
    - Tercentennial Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - WGBH Television (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - HONORARY COMMITTEE
    - Honorific Committee (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Yale Honorands (Box 6, Folder 286)
  - STEERING COMMITTEE
    - Administration (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - Invitation to Join Committee (Box 6, Folder 288)
    - Chat Room (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - 1996- 1998 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Tercentennial Steering Committee
      - 1998 Feb 19 (Box 6, Folder 291)
      - 1998 Apr 3 (Box 6, Folder 292)
      - 1998 Apr 16 (Box 6, Folder 293)
      - 1998 May 28 (Box 6, Folder 294)
      - 1998 Jun 18 (Box 6, Folder 295)
      - 1998 Sep 25 (Box 6, Folder 296)
      - 1998 Dec 3 (Box 6, Folder 297)
      - 1999 Feb 18 (Box 6, Folder 298)
      - 1999 Apr 8 (Box 6, Folder 299)
      - 1999 Jun 1 (Box 6, Folder 300)
      - 2000 Feb 17 (Box 6, Folder 301)
      - 2000 Sep 26 (Box 6, Folder 302)
      - 1999 Sep 15 (Box 6, Folder 303)
      - 2000 Apr 13 (Box 6, Folder 304)
      - 2001 Jan 23 (Box 6, Folder 305)
      - 2001 May 29 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - Yale Operations Group (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Parking (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - George H. W. Bush (Box 7, Folder 309)
  - PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT
    - Images (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - John Gambell -Images (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Yale Shots (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - FLA Code of Conduct/Sweatshops (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Chris Kule (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Tercentennial Medals (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - Merchandising (BandN Agreement) (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Merchandise Catalog (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - Merchandising for the Tercentennial (Box 7, Folder 318 - 321)
    - BAC (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - Peabody Museum (Box 7, Folder 323)
    - University Art Gallery (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - Furniture Samples (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - Contracts -Museum LIC (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - Art Resource (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - J. Peterman (Box 7, Folder 328)
  - OTHER YALE CELEBRATIONS
    - Elihu Yale's 300thBirthday (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - OTHER UNIVERSITY ANNIVERSITIES
    - Columbia University (Box 7, Folder 330)
    - Andre Breedt -University of Pretoria (Box 7, Folder 331)
    - Drexel University (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - Harvard University (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - Albertus Magnus College 70 Year Celebration (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - Appalachian State University 100 Year Celebration (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - University of Wisconsin (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - Middlebury College 200 Year Celebration (Box 7, Folder 337)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute 175 Year Celebration (Box 7, Folder 338)
    - Stanford University 100 Year Celebration (Box 7, Folder 339)
    - Washington and Lee University 250 Year Celebration (Box 7, Folder 340)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill 200 Year Celebration (Box 7, Folder 341)
    - Princeton (Box 7, Folder 342 - 343)
    - University of Pennsylvania 250 Year Celebration (Box 7, Folder 344)
    - Edinburgh Festival (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - MISCELLANOUS
    - History and Archives Committee (Box 7, Folder 346)
    - Peter Dobkin Hall (Box 7, Folder 347)
    - Linda Lorimer's Signature (Box 7, Folder 348)
    - Human Resources Training (Box 7, Folder 349)
    - LKL - "musings" Memo, 1995 August 11 (Box 7, Folder 350)
    - The Role of the University (Box 7, Folder 351)
    - Nancy Sureck (Box 7, Folder 352)
    - Events (Box 7, Folder 353)
    - Office of the Provost (Box 7, Folder 354)
    - Whitneyville Walker (Box 7, Folder 355)
    - Poet Project (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - A History of Medicine at Yale (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Publications Notes and Reference (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Bright Pages: Yale Writers 1701-2001 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - Pictorial Essay: Historic and Contemporary Pictures With Complimentary Texts (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - 300 Years of Creativity and Discovery: Yale Miscellany (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - Pictorial Essay: Hist. and Cont. Pic. w/complimentary Texts (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - Architectural (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine (Box 8, Folder 364)
    - "Yale and 20thCentury" Smith (Box 8, Folder 365)
    - Yale Worthies (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - Yale: A Short History (Box 8, Folder 367)
    - Science: History of Astronomy (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - 2001 Yale University Tercentennial Calendar (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - Tercentennial Disks (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - Science Essay (Box 8, Folder 371 - 372)
    - Science Essays -Sidney Altman (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - REVISIONS AND REPRINTS OF HISTORICA TEXTS
    - Buildings and Grounds of Yale University Revision (Box 8, Folder 374)
    - History of the Provost's Office (Box 8, Folder 375)
    - Historical Register (Box 8, Folder 376)
    - Idea of the University: A Reexamination Reprint (Box 8, Folder 377)
    - Joining the Club: A History of Jews and Yale Revision (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - Special Documents in Yale's History Compilation (Box 8, Folder 379)
    - Yale Alumni Directory Revision (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - A Yale Book of Numbers: Historical Statistics of the College and University: 1701 -2001 Revision (Box 8, Folder 381)
    - Yale: A History Reprint (Box 8, Folder 382)
    - Tercentennial Publications Meetings (Box 8, Folder 383)
    - Yale: A Celebration (Box 8, Folder 384 - 385)
  - YALE NEW HAVEN TOUR GUIDES
    - The Yale: A Guide to Yale and New Haven (Box 9, Folder 386)
    - A Campus Guide to Yale (Box 9, Folder 387)
    - Yale New Haven Illustrated History and Tour Book/Modlin (Box 9, Folder 388)
    - A Campus Guide to Yale (Continuation) (Box 9, Folder 389)
    - Michelin Guide to Yale and New Haven (Box 9, Folder 390)
    - Reference Series Meetings (Box 9, Folder 391)
    - Special Historical Documents (Box 9, Folder 392)
    - Research Publications (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - Ben Foster (Box 9, Folder 394)
    - Book of Documents (Box 9, Folder 395)
    - History of Yale Literacy Magazine (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - Brewster Book (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - Stained Glass Windows/G. Owen Bonawit (Box 9, Folder 398)
    - Student Publications (Box 9, Folder 399)
    - Yale: A Portrait (Box 9, Folder 400)
    - Yale Press (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - Science Essays (w/disk) (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - Yale Student Speak Memoirs of Yale (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Archives 300 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - History and Archives Background Proposals and Budget (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Film Preservation (Box 9, Folder 406)
  - HISTORY AND ARCHIVES SUBCOMMITTEE
    - "Yale Between the Wars" (Box 9, Folder 407)
    - Yankelovich (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - Perception of Yale -How Yale is Perceived by Nation (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - Schulman (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - KRC (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Perception Project (Box 9, Folder 412)